A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Office of Communications, Program Staff Files FA636
Rockefeller Archive Center
- David M. Davis Office Files, 1955-1971; III
  - David M. Davis Office Files -- Reports, 1962-1970
    - TCI Study -- Evaluation of International Telecommunications Routing and Distribution Systems, May 12, 1967 (Box 13)
    - Television Studio Design in Western Europe [PHOTOS], Aug 1967 (Box 13)
    - ETV Briefing -- R.M. Catalano, Dec 1967 (Box 13)
    - The College Radio Study, 1969 (Box 13)
    - Comments of the Corporation for Public Broadcasting, Sep 1969 (Box 13)
    - KCET-TV -- Feedback for Advancement -- General Report, Sep 1969 (Box 13)
    - Newsroom, Dec 1969 (Box 13)
    - Performance and Potential -- FM Reaches a Crossroads, Feb 1970 (Box 13)
    - Newsroom, Oct 1970 (Box 13)
    - The Viewing of Public Television -- 1970, Nov 1970 (Box 13)
    - The Public Television Audience, Dec 1970 (Box 13)
    - Night Call Demo Tapes, [1967-1969?] (Box 14)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Magnetic Audio Tape
    - Fourth Network Study, 1962 (Box 13)
    - Wingspread Conference on Public Television Programming, n.d. (Box 14)
    - Toward a Significant Difference -- National Project for the Improvement of Televised Instruction 1965-1968 (Box 14)
    - National Educational Television Semi-Annual Report, Jul-Dec 1968 (Box 14)
    - Comments of the Ford Foundation in Response to the Commission's Notice of Proposed Rule Making..., Oct 16, 1968 (Box 14)
    - The Public Radio Study, Apr 1969 (Box 14)
    - Educational Radio, 1967-1968 (Box 14)
    - EERN -- Radio Report, 1963 (Box 14)
    - NAB -- Annual Meeting, 1969 (Box 14)
    - NET Affiliates and Council, 1967-1968 (Box 14)
      Photos
    - Norton, Kenneth, 1964-1968 (Box 14)
    - One Nation Indivisible?, 1968-1969 (Box 14)
    - One Nation Indivisible? -- Evaluation Report, Sep 1968 (Box 14)
    - Pakistan, 1968-1969 (Box 14)
    - RMC -- Draft Dockets and Papers, 1965-1966 (Box 14)
    - Young, Elizabeth, 1968 (Box 14)
  - Community Stations -- Matching Grant Program, 1965-1968 (Box 15)
  - Sloan Commission Reports Listed in Appendix E, 1970-1971 (Box 15)
  - Sloan Commission Staff Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 15)
  - Sloan Commission on CATV -- Reports Not Included in Final Report, 1971 (Box 15)
  - Prospects and Policies for CATV, 1971 (Box 15)
  - Armsey, James W., 1971 (Box 15)
  - ITV Report -- Notes on Interviews and Visits, 1966 (Box 15)
  - ITV Weekend, 1966-1968 (Box 15)
  - ITV Commission, 1967 (Box 15)
  - Educational Technology Task Force, 1969 (Box 15)
  - Ford Foundation and Educational Television, 1967 (Box 16)
  - PE Grants Analysis, 1971 (Box 16)
  - National Programming Production and Distribution -- Fact Book, [1968] (Box 16)
  - Project for New Television Programming -- First Year Grants, 1967-1971 (Box 16)
  - David M. Davis Office Files -- Subject Files, 1955-1971
    - AL -- Birmingham ETV Commission, 1969 (Box 17)
    - AZ -- Phoenix (Tempe) KAET, 1968-1970 (Box 17)
    - AZ -- Tuscon KVAT, 1964-1971 (Box 17)
    - CA -- Los Angeles KCET, 1968-1971 (Box 17)
    - CA -- San Francisco KQED, 1965-1971 (Box 17)
    - CO -- Denver KRMA, 1968-1969 (Box 17)
    - D.C. -- Washington WETA, 1963-1971 (Box 17)
    - FL -- Jacksonville WJCT, 1964-1972 (Box 17)
    - Kentucky ETV Authority, 1971 (Box 17)
    - MD -- Owings Mills -- Maryland Center for Public Broadcasting WMPD, 1968-1971 (Box 17)
    - MI -- Detroit WTVS, 1968-1971 (Box 17)
    - NM -- Albuquerque KNME, 1970 (Box 17)
    - NY -- Binghamton WSKG, 1969 (Box 17)
    - NY -- Buffalo WNED, 1968-1969 (Box 17)
    - NY -- New York WNET, 1970 (Box 17)
    - NY -- Schenectady WMHT, 1955-1969 (Box 17)
    - NY -- Syracuse WCNY, 1963-1972 (Box 17)
    - TN -- Nashville WDCN, 1969-1970 (Box 17)
    - TX -- Dallas KERA, 1968-1971 (Box 17)
    - Virgin Islands Public Television, 1969-1971 (Box 17)
    - VA -- Norfolk WHRO, 1968-1969 (Box 17)
    - WA -- Seattle KCTS, 1968 (Box 17)
    - WA -- Spokane KSPS, 1968-1971 (Box 17)
    - WA -- Tacoma KTPS, 1970 (Box 17)
    - WV -- Morgantown WWVV, 1964-1970 (Box 17)
    - WI -- Madison WHA, 1968-1970 (Box 17)
- Correspondence, 1965-1971; IV
  - Adtel, 1969 (Box 18)
  - Advertising, 1968 (Box 18)
  - Alaska, 1969-1970 (Box 18)
  - American Broadcasting Co, 1967 (Box 18)
  - American Film Institute, 1969 (Box 18)
  - American Indians, 1968 (Box 18)
  - Arthur D. Little, Inc -- Contracts, 1969 (Box 18)
  - Bedford Stuyvesant Proposal -- ETV Station Proposal, 1966-1969 (Box 18)
  - Benavente, David, 1969 (Box 18)
  - Blacks and Media, 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Bloom, Herb, 1969 (Box 18)
  - British Leaders, 1969 (Box 18)
  - Brown, Orrin H., 1968 (Box 18)
  - CATV -- General, 1969 (Box 18)
  - Canadian Broadcasting Corp., 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Carnegie Commission, 1966 (Box 18)
  - Carnegie Corporation, 1967-1968 (Box 18)
  - CETO, 1967-1969 (Box 18)
  - Children's Programming, 1969 (Box 18)
    Slide
  - Children's TV Workshop, 1968 (Box 18)
  - Classification of ETV -- Stations and Networks (Box 18)
  - Columbia -- Summer Program -- Newsroom, 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Columbia University Editorial Policy Board, 1968 (Box 18)
  - Commercial Television, 1969 (Box 18)
  - Commonwealth Broadcasting Conference, 1969 (Box 18)
  - Communications, 1969 (Box 18)
  - Communications Company, The, 1969 (Box 18)
  - Communications Policy Issues, 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Communications Satellite Corporation, 1969 (Box 18)
  - CTV Proposal -- Boston, 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - COMSAT, 1967-1969 (Box 18)
  - Copyright, 1968-1969 (Box 19)
  - Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1967 (Box 19)
  - Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1968 (Box 19)
  - Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1969 (Box 19)
  - Corporation for Public Broadcasting, Jan-May 1969 (Box 19)
  - Corporation for Public Broadcasting, Jun-Dec 1969 (Box 19)
  - Corporation for Public Broadcasting -- Press Releases, 1969 (Box 19)
  - Corporation for Public Broadcasting -- Newsletter, 1969 (Box 19)
  - Corporation for Public Broadcasting -- Foreign Fellowship Program, 1969 (Box 19)
  - Corporation for Public Broadcasting -- Radio, 1969 (Box 19)
  - Ditchley Foundation, 1969-1970 (Box 19)
  - Dockets -- Noncommercial Television, 1969 (Box 19)
  - Drama, 1969 (Box 19)
  - Drew Associates, 1968 (Box 19)
  - EEN -- Interconnection, 1968-1969 (Box 19)
  - Educational Television Facilities Act, 1965-1969 (Box 19)
  - Educational Television Stations, 1966-1969 (Box 19)
  - Elections, 1969 (Box 19)
  - FCC -- Dockets, 1967-1969 (Box 19)
  - FCC -- General, 1966-1968 (Box 20)
  - FCC -- General, 1969 (Box 20)
  - Films -- Miscellaneous, 1968-1969 (Box 20)
  - Forum Communications Inc., 1969 (Box 20)
  - Foundations, 1969 (Box 20)
  - French Television, 1968-1969 (Box 20)
  - Fund-raising (Box 20)
  - Gillard, Frank, 1969 (Box 20)
  - Ginsburg & Feldman, 1969 (Box 20)
  - Goldin, Professor Hyman, 1969 (Box 20)
  - Graham, Beardsley, 1969 (Box 20)
  - Grants -- Noncommercial Television, 1967-1969 (Box 20)
  - Hammet & Edison, 1966-1969 (Box 20)
  - Harris, Louis & Associates, 1969 (Box 20)
  - Harris Foundation, 1969 (Box 20)
  - Health, Education and Welfare (US Department of), 1968-1969 (Box 20)
  - Institute for Politics and Planning, 1968-1969 (Box 20)
  - Instructional Television Trust -- Israel, 1969 (Box 20)
  - Interconnection, 1968 (Box 20)
  - Interconnection, 1969 (Box 20)
  - Interconnection -- Ford Foundation Submission to FCC, 1968 (Box 20)
  - Interconnection -- Submissions to FCC -- Press Releases, 1968 (Box 20)
  - Interconnection -- Submissions to FCC by Stations, Networks, etc., 1968 (Box 20)
  - ITV, 1967 (Box 21)
  - ITV (1/2), 1968 (Box 21)
  - ITV (2/2), 1968 (Box 21)
  - ITV, 1969 (Box 21)
  - Israel -- General Correspondence, 1969 (Box 21)
  - Joint Council on Educational Telecommunications (JCET), 1968-1969 (Box 21)
  - Kesselman & Kesselman Management Services Limited, 1968 (Box 21)
  - Charles F. Kettering Foundation, 1969 (Box 21)
  - Knox, William T., 1969 (Box 21)
  - Land, Herman W. -- NET Study, 1968 (Box 21)
  - Latin-American Television, 1969 (Box 21)
  - Legal Defense Fund, 1969 (Box 21)
  - Long Range Financing, 1968 (Box 21)
  - Lubell, Sam -- Channel 13, 1968 (Box 21)
  - Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 21)
  - Meetings -- Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 21)
  - Markel, Lester (Twentieth Century Fund), 1969 (Box 21)
  - Market Size, n.d. (Box 21)
  - Miller, Barbara, 1969 (Box 21)
  - Model Cities Program -- Peter S. Richards, 1968-1969 (Box 21)
  - Moreno, Cenen, 1969 (Box 21)
  - Narcotics Addiction Rehabilitation Coordinating Organization (NARCO), 1969 (Box 21)
  - National Association of Educational Broadcasters, 1968 (Box 21)
  - National Association of Educational Broadcasters, 1969 (Box 21)
  - NASA, 1969 (Box 21)
  - National Citizens Committee for Broadcasting, 1969 (Box 21)
  - National Educational Radio Correspondence, 1969 (Box 21)
  - National Instructional Television Center, 1968-1969 (Box 22)
  - Nemirow, Martin (CATV), 1968-1969 (Box 22)
  - NET Affiliates, 1969 (Box 22)
  - NET Affiliates Meeting, Apr 9-11, 1969 (Box 22)
  - NET -- Ann Arbor, 1968-1969 (Box 22)
  - NET Film Service, 1969 (Box 22)
  - NET -- Budgets, 1968-1969 (Box 22)
  - NET -- General, 1965-1968 (Box 22)
  - NET -- General, 1969 (Box 22)
  - NET -- Press Releases [PHOTOS], 1969 (Box 22)
  - NET -- Promotional Material, 1968-1969 (Box 22)
  - Newsroom Workshop, 1969 (Box 22)
  - N.I.T.C. -- Continuing Public Education Broadcasting, Sep 1969 (Box 22)
  - Office of Public Broadcasting -- Budget, 1968-1969 (Box 22)
  - Office of Public Broadcasting -- General, 1969 (Box 22)
  - Office of Public Broadcasting -- Grants, 1969 (Box 22)
  - Office of Public Broadcasting -- Fiscal Status Reports, 1969 (Box 22)
  - Office of Public Broadcasting -- Monthly Cumulative Fiscal Status Reports, 1969 (Box 22)
  - Open University, 1969 (Box 22)
  - Performance Laboratory, Inc., 1969 (Box 22)
  - Philadelphia Unused Channel, 1969 (Box 22)
  - Press Releases, 1968-1969 (Box 22)
  - Program-Related Investment, 1969 (Box 22)
  - Public Broadcasting Service, 1968 (Box 22)
  - Public Broadcasting Act -- General, 1967 (Box 22)
  - Public Broadcasting -- General, 1969 (Box 23)
  - Public Broadcasting -- Long Range Financing, 1969 (Box 23)
  - Public Broadcasting -- Program Strategy, 1969 (Box 23)
  - Public Relations, 1969 (Box 23)
  - Pugwash Meetings, 1969 (Box 23)
  - Radio -- General, 1969 (Box 23)
  - Radio -- Public Radio Network, 1968-1969 (Box 23)
  - Radio -- Student Radio, 1969 (Box 23)
  - Research, 1969 (Box 23)
  - Rochester Project, 1968 (Box 23)
  - Rostow, Walt, 1968-1969 (Box 23)
  - Satellites -- J.L. Hult Report, May 1969 (Box 23)
  - Satellites -- Alaska Conference, Aug 28-29, 1969 (Box 23)
  - Senate Hearings, 1969 (Box 23)
  - Smithsonian Institute (Council on Communications), 1969 (Box 23)
  - South Carolina ETV Commission, 1968-1971 (Box 23)
  - Speeches, 1969 (Box 23)
  - Speeches -- Bundy, 1968-1969 (Box 23)
  - Spigelman, Jim -- University of Sidney, Australia, 1969 (Box 23)
  - Stanford Proposal, 1968 (Box 23)
  - Telecommunication, 1968-1969 (Box 23)
  - Travel and Study, 1967-1969 (Box 23)
  - Trustees Meetings -- Ford Foundation, 1968-1969 (Box 23)
  - Two Bridges Neighborhood Council Cable Television, 1969 (Box 23)
  - Video Tape Recorder, 1968-1970
  - Washington Production Center, 1969 (Box 23)
  - Webster, David, 1969 (Box 23)
  - Whitney, John Hay (Whitney Foundation), 1969 (Box 23)
  - WNDT -- Network Switching Center, 1968-1969 (Box 23)
  - Whitehead, Tom -- White House, 1969 (Box 23)
- Appendix A: Reports, 1968-1971
  - Ford Foundation; International Division -- Proposed Budget, Fiscal Year 1969, Jun 1968 (Report #019918)
  - Ford Foundation; Management Costs, Sep 1968 (Report #019919)
  - Ford Foundation Office of Public Broadcasting; Washington, D.C. Newsroom, May 1971 (Report #019920)